(Bernadette:)Okay, so you met this girl,
you exchanged numbers,
(Bernadette:)and you're gonna
meet up with her.
(Raj:)Just to help her
with her screenplay.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Well,
I guess that's not so bad.
(Howard:)You weren't there.
(Howard:)He was really flirting.
(Raj:)Hey, it's not my fault
if American women project
(Raj:)their fantasies on foreigners
(Raj:)with the kind of magical voice
that grants wishes.
(Bernadette:)I'm sure it was harmless.
(Bernadette:)People flirt. No big deal.
(Howard:)Really? So it's
okay if I fl...
(Bernadette:)Not you. I own your ass.
(Bernadette:)The real question is,
where are you with Emily?
(Raj:)Uh, it's hard to say.
(Raj:)I think we're good,
but things like this
(Raj:)make me wonder if Emily's
really the right person for me.
(Raj:)I mean, did you guys ever have
doubts about each other?
(Howard:)No. Never.
Absolutely.
(Howard:)What?
(Bernadette:)Howie, you forget
(Bernadette:)how much of our early dates
(Bernadette:)involved you doing magic
(Bernadette:)and me doing this.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Howard:)I had reservations
about you, too.
(Bernadette:)No, you didn't.
(Howard:)No, I didn't.
(Bernadette:)Well, it doesn't matter now,